leadershipconnect.io 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy | Leadership Connect

Leadership Connect respects your privacy. We do not collect personal information on this website unless you choose to provide this information to us.

### Non-Personal Data

When you visit our website, we do collect non-personal data such as:

  * Your domain name;
  * The type of browser or operating system you use;
  * The date and time you accessed our site;
  * Any site through which you accessed our site;
  * The pages you visited and how much time you spent on each page.

This information does not personally identify you. We aggregate this information for internal use. By collecting this information, we hope to improve our website and better serve you.

### Use of Subscription and Registration Information

If you choose to place orders, request information, or contact us, we will not be able to process your request unless you provide us your contact details. A separate subscription agreement will govern the terms of our use of your personal information. In general, information gathered will be primarily for the internal use of Leadership Connect and may be used to contact visitors for marketing purposes. If you purchase a subscription, we may occasionally provide your name and mailing address to qualified third parties whom we have determined offer products or services that may be of interest to you.

Our website has links to other websites, such as government agencies, private organizations, foreign governments and international organizations.

Please be aware that:

  * If you access another site through a link we provide, you are subject to the privacy policy of that site.
  * Any reference on such other website to commercial products, services, manufacturers, or companies does not constitute an endorsement by Leadership Connect.
  * Leadership Connect is not responsible for the contents of any pages to which you link from our website.

If you do not wish to receive our marketing materials (besides subscription renewal notices) and/or any offers from qualified third parties, please unsubscribe from the email or [contact us](https://www.leadershipconnect.io/company/contact-us/).

### Third Parties

From time-to-time, Leadership Connect may engage third parties, such as Google Analytics and Google Adwords, to analyze usage and volume statistical information from users who visit Leadership Connect’s website as well as track conversions of the ads we run on Google. The information provided to third parties does not include personal information, but this information may be re-associated with personal information after Leadership Connect receives it.

This privacy policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on our website. Please check back periodically for updates.
